I eat an entire pint of ice cream every
single day and still maintain a caloric
deficit. Here are some of the recipes I
made this week to stay fit and hit my
protein goal. Started it off with a
matcha protein ice cream. One of my
all-time favorite recipes. Tastes just
like a matcha latte and the macros are
borderline unbelievable. Then I
recreated my favorite Ben & Jerry's
flavor. Halfbaked chocolate base with
brownie pieces and cookie dough bites.
Then I wanted to bring a Ben & Jerry's
flavor back from the flavor graveyard.
This was cinnamon buttons, which was a
cinnamon base with little cinnamon roll
bites. Then I had to run back my
Superman Blizzard flavor. This is a cake
batter cookie dough blizzard, and it's
one of my favorite recipes of all time.
Kind of pissed they already took it off
the DQ menu, but at least we have this
to recreate it. And then ended off the
week by remaking one of my most
polarizing recipes of all time, brownie
batter, aka the rusty pipe. You either
love it or actually everyone that truly
makes the recipe loves it. So, you can't
always judge a book by its cover. All
these recipes are posted right here on
my page.